<resources>
    <string name="AppName">Vector calculator</string>
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-7928726493812110/9219867188</string>
    <string name="test_banner">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>
    <string name="answer_window_faq">Enter an expression.</string>
    <string name="answer_window_faq_memory">The memory is empty.</string>
    <string name="answer_window_error">Parameters are not valid!</string>
    <string name="history_title">HISTORY</string>
    <string name="history_answer">answer</string>
    <string name="history_input">input</string>
    <string name="history_date">date</string>
    <string name="idString">idString</string>
    <string name="idInteger">idInteger</string>
    <string name="clear_historyTitle">Clear all.</string>

    <string name="msg1">Addition / subtraction.</string>
    <string name="msg2">Decomposition of a vector.</string>
    <string name="msg3">Scalar multiplication.</string>
    <string name="msg4">Vector multiplication.</string>
    <string name="msg5">Mixed multiplication.</string>
    <string name="msg6">Multiplication / division by scalar.</string>
    <string name="msg7">Distance between vectors.</string>
    <string name="msg8">The angle between the vector and the x, y, z axes.</string>

    <string name="instructionNumbers">The main numeric keypad.</string>
    <string name="instructionsPoint">Delimiter for entering the fractional part.</string>
    <string name="instructionCaret">
        Separator for entering the value of the angle (phase) of the vector.\n
        For example: 10.123 ^ 45.123
    </string>
    <string name="instructionPlusMinus">
        Operators for calculating the sum (difference) of vectors.\n
        The input of the number of vectors is unlimited.\n
        For example: 10.123 ^ 10.123 + 10.123 ^ 10.123 = 20.2460 ^ 10.1230
    </string>
    <string name="instructionVectorMultiple">
        The operator for computing vector multiplication.\n
        Only 2 vectors are entered in the operation.\n
        The answer is equal to the area of the parallelogram constructed on the introduced vectors.\n
        For example: 10 ^ 10X10 ^ 60 = -76.6044.
    </string>
    <string name="instructionDevOnScalar">
        The operator for computing the division of a vector into a scalar.\n
        For example: 10 ^ 10/2 = 5 ^ 10.
    </string>
    <string name="instructionScalarMultiple">
        The operator for computing scalar multiplication of vectors.\n
        Only 2 vectors are entered in the operation.\n
        For example: 10 ^ 10 * 10 ^ 60 = 64.2788.\n
        It is possible to multiply a vector by a scalar.\n
        For example: 10 ^ 10 * 10 = 100 ^ 10.
    </string>
    <string name="instruction_decomposition">
        The operator of the expansion of vectors into 2 nearest angles.\n
        c: a: b \n
        c is the source vector;\n
        a, b - vector, the amplitude of which will be calculated.\n
        For example: 1000 ^ 45: 85: 10 \n
        = 1000 ^ 45: 593.6957 ^ 85.0: 665.437 ^ 10.0.\n
        An error about the collinearity of vectors,\n
        If the angle between the vectors a and b is 180 degrees.
    </string>
    <string name="instructionFindDistance">
        The operator of calculating the distance between vectors.\n
        Only 2 vectors are entered in the operation.\n
        For example, 10 ^ 10dis30 ^ 50 = 23.2459.
    </string>
    <string name="instructionFindAngle">
        The operator of calculating the angle between the vector and the axes of the coordinates X, Y, Z.\n
        In the operation, only 1 vector is entered.\n
        The vector is entered in the format (x; y; z).\n
        For example, angle (10; 34; 78) = \n
        OX (83.3) OY (66.62) OZ (24.44).\n
        The answer is in degrees.\n
    </string>
    <string name="instructionGraph">
        Opens the schedule screen.\n
        Graph of the sum (difference), decomposition of vectors.\n
        It is intended for visual representation of the performed actions with vectors\n
        Vectors are displayed in scale relative to the screen size of the telephone.\n
        Near each vector, information about the vector is displayed in the form of an amplitude ^ angle.\n
        The number of displayed vectors is infinite.
    </string>
    <string name="instruction_scobes">
        Additional elements of the input expression.\n
        Used in the following functions:\n
        1. Calculation of the angle;\n
        2. Mixed multiplication:\n
        (x;y;z)(x;y;z)(x;y;z);\n
        Example:(10;23;78)(32;87;90)(54;98;12)\n
        = -96648.0.\n
        The result of the introduced expression is the determinant of the matrix 3x3:\n
        10 23 78\n
        32 87 90\n
        54 98 12
    </string>
    <string name="instruction_semicolon">
        Additional elements of the input expression.\n
        Used in the following functions:\n
        1. Mixed multiplication;\n
        2. Calculation of the angle;\n
    </string>
    <string name="instruction_cursor">
        Cursor control in the expression input window.\n
        You can select the position of the cursor by clicking on the place of interest in the expression.\n
        The input is made to the left of the cursor.
    </string>
    <string name="instruction_clear">
        Complete cleaning of the input field.
    </string>
    <string name="instruction_del">
        Delete the character to the left of the cursor.
    </string>
    <string name="instruction_memory_plus">
        Adding the calculation result to the contents of the memory. \n
        It is used only in operations with scalar data and vectors. \n
        For example, in memory 10 ^ 10, only a vector can be added to the given memory content in the form of an amplitude ^ angle. \n
        For example, in memory 10, only a scalar can be added to this memory content.
    </string>
    <string name="instruction_memory_minus">
        Subtraction (difference) of the calculation result to the contents of memory.\n
        It is used only in operations with scalar data and vectors.\n
        For example, in memory 10 ^ 10, only the vector in the form of the amplitude ^ angle can be subtracted from this memory content. \n
        For example, in memory 10, only the scalar can be subtracted from this memory content.
    </string>
    <string name="instruction_memory_clean">
        Clearing the contents of memory.
    </string>
    <string name="instruction_memory_read">
        Output the contents of memory in the response window.
    </string>
    <string name="instructionHistory">
        History of calculations. \n
        Clicking on the history item will copy its contents to the input and response windows. \n
        The previously entered data in the input and response window will be erased and replaced with the history item information.
    </string>
    <string name="msgNextInApp">
        The application is constantly being updated and new functions are added. \n
        If you have any suggestions on how to modify the application, or if you find an error in the calculation,
        please report in the comments on the application page.
    </string>
</resources>
